I can say like this that do you want to know what it was like for us to step into this apartment
For the first time, we have done a pod about this that you can listen to.
There is also a video odd so you can watch it if you want to do it.
What is so special to be here and talk about memories with our one sister.
Who started telling memories that didn't even remember.
It was totally sick.
I don't even remember the paranormal memories, I've suppressed them.
So there are certainly more memories inside the head of one, but they are gone.
-But it is special to be back and we have to thank those who have the apartment today.
That we may come here.
Because the apartment itself is not haunted right now.
We always go to places where it is said that a lot of things happen.
- You sit in an active corner then when we lived here.
Right in that corner there were a lot of things that happened, we had a guitar.
We had a guitar that was here and then ...
What I was told that I forgot about was the paranormal event that
Someone played on those guitars when I was home alone, so I panicked.
And this I don't remember, I've probably suppressed it.
- Mom, if you're here with us
can you touch this white
The thing that is on the chair here?
Can you go past it once only?
Can you do it now?
Then we take red as “no”
and green as "yes".
Peter, do you see the lamp that flashes there now?
Can you go to it?
If you leave it there and go to the next?
Or is it Irene who has come here now?
So I was completely breathless only I went to the kitchen.
My eyes just run.
This is really strange.
- It would have been interesting that if it continues if we remove it from the field there ...
We try, then maybe I happen to touch this one just.
I understand how much that
- I'm completely exhausted.
I don't know what it is, if it is an emotional storm that is going on in the skull now.
- I don't want to sit down.
I want to stand, but will see if I can fit because it is quite crowded in here.
This was my room when I lived here.
And I saw those plaster figures that slid over the floor.
We start communication here as well, but you can go to the blue vibrant light.
What was that?
- I trampled on something.
- But you can go to the blue pulsating light if you want.
Or pass just above.
To the floor here where it flashes blue?
- Peter
You were recently
And talked to us, we think it was you who came through.
And we haven't talked to you for a long time.
You have come through a little neighbor now and then.
But can you come in here too?
Do you see this game box standing on the bench?
If you touch it
Then it will play a little neighbor.
Do you see what lies and flashes on the floor?
Make it shine green for "yes" for example.
And red for "no".
As our sister Tina received in Christmas present
by you Johanna, you can pull past
On the floor here now where it flashes blue.
No, we don't get anything on the instruments in this room either.
- We are testing one more room.
- Should we try your room across?
Here's your room.
You had an experience in bed where you felt like someone locked you.
- Yes, it was not like Peter and Johanna.
It felt like something else.
It can come from all the different Ouija boards used.
Everything cracked you did as younger, that you brought something with you.
What happens when we are in your room over there you had and in my room here
is that all rooms seem to lean in different directions.
It is a very strange feeling that it is leaning.
It feels like this room is leaning there.
If I had released a bullet now, it would have felt like it would stick in that direction.
- It is also interesting with the tone we have.
Do you notice it?
We talk pretty quietly, pretty
Almost like a library.
It is not a higher volume, we keep fairly even
Monoton's voice, I don't know what it is, if it's because we're just at home.
"home"
And talking to family.
- I think this is built into our system in ourselves.
You could have this tone here, otherwise it was heard down to the neighbor.
I think so, you couldn't talk higher because then the neighbor started knocking or stomping.
I think I saw a tennis ball on a floor here.
I think if I put it on the table as we have a case here
with a tennis ball.
I go and pick it up.
There is one here too.
A slightly larger tennis ball.
There you can see that it also settled.
- there we have a ball
Who has thrown in this apartment several times when we lived here.
Can the person who did it, throw this ball?
Get it to move, roll down on the floor.
- We have people we have met on here outside
You do not know what it is you really feel, you become very
drained, tired and a dizziness that you also felt before.
Is it paranormal or for a natural cause just because we are here?
And that we do something that we are not so used to.
To actually seek contact with our own.
- And what may make you hold back a little.
It feels right to do this.
Without them to come to one when they want to do it themselves.
- but the interesting thing is that
which we start to see here now litigran to
We don't get much.
- And see if it is stronger on the site.
But something that is very interesting is why it is just that corner.
The guitars, the plaster figure, Jojon are from this place.
- So there can be something else then.
- It may have been a portal that has been there for any length of time.
So that this is where the energies have come through as strongly.
So this is also the case that when we sit here ...
I feel this that
In a way I'm glad they're not here now
if you understand what I mean.
That they can visit us when they want to.